The brushes, ink, paper, and inkstones
the Eldest Lady uses daily
are all gone.
Why do you arbitrarily withhold them?
It's not like we're starving her.
Why are you
yelling so loud?
That mother and daughter
are simply going too far.
Xiaolan,
let it go.
Not only did they take your painting,
but now they won't even
let you use paper and brushes.
This painting of the Phoenix Nirvana
is made of a special canvas.
Even with brushes, ink,
paper, and inkstones,
it would probably be hard to restore.
Good job.
Wan,
it has been a while.
I hope you have been well.
Young Master Chu,
what brings you here?
I
came to give you these writing
materials.
I have heard this painting
is very important to you, Wan.
If it is damaged and needs restoration,
I am willing to help take a look.
How did you know about this?
Lady Keying absolutely did not
send me here.
Young Master Chu,
you are just like when we were kids.
You still cannot lie.
Xue Keying,
come out.
What are you scheming now?
How could I be scheming anything?
I have heard that
you and Young Master Chu
are childhood friends.
He is handsome and skilled at painting.
I just wanted
to create an opportunity for you two
to catch up.
Xiaolan, return the things to her.
Let's go.
When courting a girl,
you must be indirect,
subtle,
and play hard to get.
Why are you so straightforward?
Lady Keying, please don't say that.
I, Chu,
have always behaved properly.
I have never had
any improper thoughts about your sister.
Why are you claiming the friend zone card
yourself?
Are you the male lead or not?
I did go against you
in every way before,
but I'm not
who I used to be.
Let's get along peacefully from now on.
Who would believe that?
How can you not believe me?
I'm really here to help you.
Ning Yuanci is a total scumbag.
He only married you
to control the Xue family
through the alliance.
Of course I know
he's no good.
You're so devoted to him,
but has he ever changed a bit for you?
You see it quite clearly, don't you?
Then why don't you
reject him
and find your official match?
What is an official match?
Someone who truly loves you.
Someone who cares for you,
understands you,
loves you back,
and is willing to spend
their life with you.
Like
Chu Qingyun, for example.
I indeed don't like Ning Yuanci,
nor do I want to marry him.
But that doesn't mean
I have to like another man.
Mutual understanding
and love
are nothing but illusions.
Instead of relying on others,
it's better to rely on myself.
You don't need to worry
about my affairs anymore,
sister.
What a strong female lead speech.
She delivers her lines
even smoother than I do.
Let's go.
This woman...
How can I make her
listen to me?
What's your relationship
with Chu Qingjun?
What does my relationship with him
have to do with you?
If you don't tell me,
he won't live to see
tomorrow.
Are you my dad?
Why are you so controlling?
That's inappropriate.
So much for your
so-called sincerity.
You heard I'm marrying Xue Ruowan,
so you immediately turn around
and flirt with another man,
huh?
What did you expect?
Not all women
will wait around for you
forever.
Just because I don't like you,
doesn't mean I'll immediately
find another man.
Whatever I said
or did to you
before,
it was all an illusion.
Rather than pinning my hopes
on a man like you,
I'd be better off alone.
My Lady,
are you sure you want to do this?
As things stand,
there is no other way.
I am just worried it is too dangerous.
If I flee the marriage,
it will implicate the entire Xue family.
If I die,
perhaps
Ning Yuanci will
spare my father and the others.
Sister is in poor health,
and should stay in her room more.
But you, as her maid,
always take her out for walks.
Always with this attitude.
What did you say?
I will slap your face!
Xiaolan,
my daily medicine
hasn't been brewed yet.
Go check on it quickly.
We cannot delay.
Yes, My Lady.
Xiaolan
has been with me since childhood
and is deeply loyal.
Sister, please do not make
things difficult for her.
These servants are failing
in their duties.
Let me
take good care of you, sister.
No need.
How could I trouble you?
I'm afraid I don't deserve it.
Oh, you deserve it.
Let me massage your legs
and see if they
really have no feeling at all.
It's just playing the villainess.
How hard can it be?
I can act
better than Xue Keying 1.0.
Enough.
Just hit me
or scold me
as you usually do.
Watching you act like this
is exhausting.
If there's nothing else,
I'll go back to rest.
Is it because my performance
lacks depth?
Watch out, Second Lady!
The bamboo scaffold is collapsing!
What are you doing?
Second Lady,
are you alright?
Who told you to put it here?
Put it over there.
I deserve to die.
I'll have it removed right away.
Are you okay?
Why are you looking at me like that?
I'm the one who saved you.
After dealing with the assassins,
I still have to prevent Xue Ruowan
from falling into the lake.
I really am the busiest second
female lead in this whole drama.
Tonight,
I'm going to guard the lake myself.
Let's see who dares to come.
I surrender. Don't kill me.
Even Cui Hu couldn't beat the thugs.
I shouldn't even try.
It's you.
Why are you always following me?
Didn't I tell you
to stay away from me?
that I married your sister
to comply with His Majesty's will?
I don't like her at all.
You are different
from her in my heart.
Stop right there.
I really can't stand hearing this.
Not this again.
Can't you come up with something new?
I have real business to attend to.
Serving you
is not part of my business.
From now on,
you
keep your distance
from me.
In the past,
you were always the one
getting close to me.
Now
you are so cold.
Do you have a new sweetheart?
What does it matter
if I have a sweetheart or not?
Playing the gentle and affectionate role,
aren't you just trying to trick me
and use me as a tool?
The sound of falling into the water.
No way.
Oh no!
Somebody come!
My Lady has fallen into the lake!
Somebody!
Help!
What happened? What happened?
My Lady fell into the lake!
Xue Ruowan!
Somebody come quickly!
My Lady fell into the lake!
Help!
Quick,
grab the branch!
Somebody come!
Help! My Lady fell into the lake!
Xiaolan!
Don't just stand there.
Save her!
I-I can't swim.
Somebody come!
Call for help!
My Lady fell into the water!
Somebody come!
Forget it.
Save her!
I'll do it myself.
My Lady fell into the water!
This way.
Come.
Slow down. Slow down.
Hold on.
Quick.
Hold on tight.